Guide to the Stuart Elliott papers, 1875-2014 and undated RL.11108
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Writings File, 1969-2014 and undated; 7
  - 2008, 3
    - 8/18--ABC/TV Guide, 2008 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - 8/19--Olympics and women viewers, 2008 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - 8/20--Olympics, 2008 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - 8/21--Core brands, 2008 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - 8/25--Olympics ad reviews, 2008 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - 9/2--Twenty questions, 2008 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - 9/3--Saks/Bloomingdale's, 2008 (Box 63, Folder 3-4)
    - 9/5--Dexter, 2008 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - 9/5--Eepybird/Samurai Girl, 2008 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - 9/8--Magazines, 2008 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - 9/8--Nationwide/Sanjaya, 2008 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - 9/11--Jack + Bill, 2008 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - 9/11--MTV/Hewlett Packard, 2008 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - 9/12--Nationwide/Sanjaya, 2008 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - 9/12-10/6--Halloween, 2008 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - 9/15--Logo/Levi's, 2008 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - 9/15--Nielsen placement report, 2008 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - 9/16--Jack + Bill/Pop-up agencies, 2008 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - 9/18--Microsoft/Crispin Porter Bogusky, 2008; 2 folders (Box 64, Folder 4-5)
    - 9/20--Saks/Lord Taylor, 2008 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - 9/22--Advertising and economic volatility, 2008 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - 9/23--Red Roof Inn, 2008 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - 9/24--Christmas, 2008 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - 9/26--Milk, 2008 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - 9/29--Advertising Week, 2008 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - 9/29--Pushing Daisies (series), 2008 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - 9/30--Wachovia/Ogilvy Mather, 2008 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - 10/2--Bud Light, 2008 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - 10/3--Atlantic/Economist magazines, 2008 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - 10/7--Old tobacco advertising, 2008 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - 10/8--Ad Council/GLSEN (Gay, Lesbian and Straight Education Network), 2008 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - 10/14--Halloween/Wal-Mart, 2008 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - 10/15--Economic impact outside, 2008 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - 10/20--ANA Conference, 2008 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - 10/21--ANA Conference, 2008 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - 10/24--"Bargain" as buzzword, 2008 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - 10/28--Advertising as a career for television characters, 2008 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - 10/28--Mad Men (series), 2008 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - 10/31--Bloomingdale's/Infiniti, 2008 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - 10/31--Starbucks, 2008 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - 11/4--Negative advertising, 2008 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - 11/6--GSN (Game Show Network), 2008 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - 11/6--Post-election advertising, 2008 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - 11/7--Big event TV, 2008 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - 11/7--Madison Avenue economic pain, 2008 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - 11/10--More value less glamor, 2008 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - 11/11--Countybank, 2008 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - 11/11--Local TV blues, 2008 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - 11/11--U.S. Army ad campaign, 2008 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - 11/13--Commercial Closet Association, 2008 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - 11/13--Holiday retail, 2008 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - 11/17--Dandelion (Firm), 2008 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - 11/17-18--BBDO/Pepsi, 2008 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - 11/18--Golden Goggle Awards, 2008 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - 11/20--Walgreen's, 2008 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - 11/24--Obama/O-mania, 2008 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - 11/25--Money as incentive: Sweepstakes, game shows, etc., 2008 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - 12/1--Twenty questions, 2008 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - 12/1--Apple/Simpsons, 2008 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - 12/2--Stove Top, 2008 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - 12/4--Coupons, 2008 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - 12/4--Super Bowl, 2008 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - 12/5--Shrek, 2008 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - 12/8--Automobile advertising, 2008 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - 12/9--Forecast, 2008 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - 12/10--Jay Leno in prime-time, 2008 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - 12/10--Super Bowl/Audi, 2008 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - 12/15--Banks, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - 12/17--Religion, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - 12/19--Omnicom, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - 12/19--Barak Obama/Mentor a Child, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - 12/22--Spike TV/120 Live, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - 12/29--Best and worst, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - ANA curtain riser, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - NFL, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Post-Upfronts, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Super Bowl, 2008; 3 folders (Box 68, Folder 10-13)
    - Super Bowl--Anheuser-Busch, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Super Bowl--Audi, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Super Bowl--CareerBuilder, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Super Bowl--Cars.com, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Super Bowl--Coca-Cola, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Super Bowl--Dell, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Super Bowl--E*Trade, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Super Bowl--General Motors, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - Super Bowl--Hershey, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - Super Bowl--Hyundai, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 23)
    - Super Bowl--Movie ads, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 24)
    - Super Bowl--New York Times coverage, 2008 (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - Super Bowl--ONDCP anti-drug spot, 2008 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Super Bowl--Pepsi/Sobe Lifewater, 2008 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Super Bowl--Procter Gamble, 2008 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Super Bowl--T-Mobile, 2008 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Super Bowl--Taco Bell, 2008 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Super Bowl--Under Armour, 2008 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Super Bowl--Unilever/Sunsilk, 2008 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Super Bowl--Victoria's Secret, 2008 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Super Bowl--Wal-Mart, 2008 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Upfronts, 2008 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - 2009, 4
    - 1/1--Race, 2009 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - 1/4--Neuro-marketing, 2009 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - 1/8--Tropicana, 2009 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - 1/12--Honda, 2009 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - 1/13--Intel, 2009 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - 1/14--Denny's, 2009 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - 1/15-20--Presidential ads, 2009 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - 1/16--Esquire and Discovery, 2009 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - 1/22--TNT: Trust Me (series), 2009 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - 1/23--Super Bowl, 2009 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - 1/26--Prayers for Bobby (film) and ads, 2009 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - 1/28--Super Bowl, 2009 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - 1/30--Super Bowl preview, 2009 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - 2/2--Super Bowl review, 2009 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - 2/3--Super Bowl post-game, 2009 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - 2/4--Doritos, 2009 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - 2/6--Grammys, 2009 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - 2/6--Super Bowl, 2009 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - 2/9--Liquor ads on TV, 2009 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - 2/10--Bob Lachky/Anheuser-Busch, 2009 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - 2/10--Doritos, 2009 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - 2/11--Pepsi logo, 2009 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - 2/19--Geico, 2009 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - 2/20--Academy Awards (Oscars), 2009 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - 2/23--Tropicana, 2009 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - 2/24--Academy Awards (Oscars), 2009 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - 3/3--Snickers/Snacklish, 2009 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - 3/5--TAP Project, 2009 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - 3/9--Liquor moderation ads, 2009 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - 3/10--Quaker Oats, 2009 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - 3/12--Magazine cover advertising, 2009 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - 3/13--Honda Insight, 2009 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - 3/16--Sci Fi Channel/Sy Fy, 2009 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - 3/17--Disney Kids (series), 2009 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - 3/18--Sears, 2009 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - 3/19--Saturn automobiles, 2009 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - 3/23--Robert J. Coen/Brian Wieser (Magna), 2009 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - 3/25--Diversity in the ad industry, 2009 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - 3/25--New products in tough times, 2009 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - 3/30--Liberty Mutual, 2009 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - 3/31--Special Olympics, 2009 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - 3/31--TiVo study, 2009 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - 4/1--Vitamin Water, 2009 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - 4/3--ConAgra/Healthy Choice, 2009 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - 4/6--Nissan Cube, 2009 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - 4/7--Nostalgia in ads, 2009 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - 4/10--Burger King/SpongeBob, 2009 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - 4/11--Trust Me (series), 2009 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - 4/13--Nationwide, 2009 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - 4/13--Retail, 2009 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - 4/16--"Stimulus" in ads, 2009 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - 4/20--Baby boomers, 2009 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - 4/22--AFLAC, 2009 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - 4/28--AT, 2009 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - 4/28--Retail percentage discounting, 2009 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - 4/29--Sony Crackle.com, 2009 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - 4/30--Condoms, 2009 (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - 5/1--Fashion Show (series), 2009 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - 5/3--CBS Upfront, 2009 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - 5/8--30 Rock (series), 2009 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - 5/10--Cable television, 2009 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - 5/11--"Value" as a marketing term, 2009 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - 5/14--Optimedia, 2009 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - 5/15--Populism/ranting, 2009; 2 folders (Box 74, Folder 6-7)
    - 5/18--Telemundo Upfront, 2009 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - 5/18--TV Upfronts, 2009; 2 folders (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - 5/19--ESPN Upfront, 2009 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - 5/19--TV Upfronts, 2009; 2 folders (Box 74, Folder 11-12)
    - 5/20--George Lopez, 2009 (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - 5/20--TV Upfronts, 2009 (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - 5/21--TV Upfronts, 2009 (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - 5/22--TV Upfronts, 2009 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - 5/26--TV Upfronts, 2009 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - 5/29--Great Depression as an advertising trope, 2009 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - 6/2--General Motors, 2009 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - 6/3--Advertising to savers, 2009 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - 6/5--Microsoft Bing, 2009 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - 6/8-10--Nielsen/Ad spending, 2009 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - 6/9--Diversity in radio/William Thompson, 2009 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - 6/11--Crispin Porter Bogusky (CPB Europe), 2009 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - 6/11--Omega/Moon landing anniversary, 2009 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - 6/12--Buick, 2009 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - 6/15--Carspaze, 2009 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - 6/15--Cinema advertising, 2009 (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - 6/15--U.S. flag on t-shirts, 2009 (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - 6/16--Ace Metrix, 2009 (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - 6/16--Price Waterhouse Coopers/Digital media, 2009 (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - 6/17--60s revivalism in advertising, 2009 (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - 6/17--Charles Schwab, 2009 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - 6/17--MDCU/Advertising education, 2009 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - 6/18--Gas Station TV, FuelCast, etc., 2009 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - 6/19--Ebay, 2009 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - 6/23--Alice.com, 2009 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - 6/23--TiVo/Quantcast, 2009 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - 6/24--Sapient/Nitro Group, 2009 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - 6/25--Summer travel, 2009 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - 6/25--Wal-Mart/Disney, 2009 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - 6/26--Michael Jackson, 2009 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - 6/29--Billy Mays, 2009 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - 6/29--Orbitz, 2009 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - 6/30--Levi Strauss, 2009 (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - 6/30--U.S. Tobacco/Leo Burnett, 2009 (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - 7/1--Ad Council, 2009 (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - 7/1--Pepsi, 2009 (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - 7/1--Tanqueray, 2009 (Box 76, Folder 17)
    - 7/6--20 questions, 2009 (Box 76, Folder 18)
    - 7/6--Out.com/Dancing with the Stars, 2009 (Box 76, Folder 19)
    - 7/6--StoreBoard Media, 2009 (Box 76, Folder 20)
    - 7/7--School of Visual Arts, 2009 (Box 76, Folder 21)
    - 7/8--Famous Footwear, 2009 (Box 76, Folder 22)
    - 7/8--J.C. Penney, 2009 (Box 76, Folder 23)
    - 7/9--Connecticut casinos, 2009 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - 7/10--Mad Men (series), 2009 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - 7/13--MinneADpolis, 2009 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - 8--TV Upfronts, 2009; 2 folders (Box 77, Folder 4-5)
    - 8/4--Expedia.com, 2009 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - 8/6--TV Upfronts, 2009 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - 8/7--House (series), 2009 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - 8/7--UPS, 2009 (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - 8/9--Razorfish/Publicis, 2009 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - 8/10--House Beautiful, 2009 (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - 8/12--Bloomingdale's, 2009 (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - 8/13--Gap, 2009 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - 8/14--Nielsen/CIMM, 2009 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - 8/18--Sony, 2009 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - 8/21--Miller Time, 2009 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - 8/24--Furniture, 2009 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - 8/25--Advertising Walk of Fame, 2009 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - 8/25--PETA, 2009 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - 8/25--Vampire Diaries (series), 2009 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - 8/26--Barbie, 2009 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - 8/27--Oreo/Donald Trump, 2009 (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - 8/28--Get a Job, 2009 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - 8/28--Hot Wheels Battle Force 5, 2009 (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - 8/31--Campbell's Chunky Soup, 2009 (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - 9/3--Target, 2009 (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - 9/8--Power of print, 2009 (Box 78, Folder 15)
    - 9/10--Jameson whiskey, 2009 (Box 78, Folder 16)
    - 9/11--Video Music Awards, 2009 (Box 78, Folder 17)
    - 9/14--B.F. Goodrich, 2009 (Box 78, Folder 18)
    - 9/14--GoDaddy, 2009 (Box 78, Folder 19)
    - 9/14--Jay Leno, 2009 (Box 78, Folder 20)
    - 9/14--Mad Men (series), 2009 (Box 78, Folder 21)
    - 9/16--Michael Jeary, 2009 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - 9/16--MSN The Wrap (series), 2009 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - 9/17--Guns, 2009 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - 9/18--Dannon, 2009 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - 9/18--InterBrand, 2009 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - 9/20--Helayne Spivak, 2009 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - 9/22--Advertising Walk of Fame, 2009 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - 9/23--Advertising Week, 2009 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - 9/23--Times Square, 2009 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - 9/24--Big Ad Gig, 2009 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - 9/24--Mad Men/Dr. Pepper, 2009 (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - 9/24--UPS, 2009 (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - 9/29--Advertising Research Foundation, 2009 (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - 9/29--Super Bowl, 2009 (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - 9/30--Pink Papers, 2009 (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - 10/1--Mrs. Butterworth, 2009 (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - 10/2--Pizza Hut, 2009 (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - 10/5--Digital media ad spending, 2009 (Box 79, Folder 18)
    - 10/5--Levi Strauss, 2009 (Box 79, Folder 19)
    - 10/5--Milkbone, 2009 (Box 79, Folder 20)
    - 10/6--Conde Nast, 2009 (Box 79, Folder 21)
    - 10/6--Michelin, 2009 (Box 79, Folder 22)
    - 10/7--Basic brands, 2009 (Box 79, Folder 23)
    - 10/7--Wendy's, 2009 (Box 79, Folder 24)
    - 10/8--Dave Letterman, 2009 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - 10/8--Subaru, 2009 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - 10/9--Cadillac, 2009 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - 10/12--CIGNA, 2009 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - 10/13--Magna/Forecasting, 2009 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - 10/13--Spanish agencies, 2009 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - 10/14--Old Navy/Carrie Donovan, 2009 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - 10/14--Olympics, 2009 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - 10/15--Anheuser-Busch/Saturday Night Live, 2009 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - 10/15--Lowe/Deutsch merger, 2009 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - 10/15--Porsche Panamera, 2009 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - 10/16--Discovery, 2009 (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - 10/16--Where the Wild Things Are, 2009 (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - 10/17--Mad Men (series), 2009 (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - 10/19--Brand Affinities Technologies, 2009 (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - 10/21--Conde Nast, 2009 (Box 80, Folder 16)
    - 10/22--Microsoft, 2009 (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - 10/23--Dove Chocolate/Martha Stewart, 2009 (Box 80, Folder 18)
    - 10/23--USA Network, 2009 (Box 80, Folder 19)
    - 10/23--VW/Deutsch, 2009 (Box 80, Folder 20)
    - 10/26--Daffy's, 2009 (Box 80, Folder 21)
    - 10/26--Microsoft/Fox/Family Guy, 2009 (Box 80, Folder 22)
    - 10/27--Macy's/J.C. Penney holiday, 2009 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - 10/28--Interpublic/IPGLBT, 2009 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - 10/29--Crowdsourcing, 2009 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - 10/30--New York Co./J. C. Penney, 2009 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - 11/1--Sun Life, 2009 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - 11/2--CBS/Super Bowl/Card.com, 2009 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - 11/2--State Farm, 2009 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - 11/3--2010, 2009 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - 11/3--Cliff Freeman, 2009 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - 11/9--ANA/Masters of Marketing conference, 2009; 2 folders (Box 81, Folder 10-11)
    - 11/11--Spike TV, 2009 (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - 11/12--Captain Morgan/NFL, 2009 (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - 11/12--Cause marketing, 2009 (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - 11/12--Gap Christmas, 2009 (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - 11/12--Guitar Hero, 2009 (Box 81, Folder 16)
    - 11/16--Detroit, 2009 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - 11/16--Orbit gum, 2009 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - 11/17--McCann/Mad Men, 2009 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - 11/18--NYC Company, 2009 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - 11/19--Graffiti, 2009 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - 11/20--Disney/xBox/Jonas Brothers, 2009 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - 11/23--AOL, 2009 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - 11/24--NBCUniversal Digital Studio, 2009 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - 11/25--Christmas, 2009 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - 11/25--Product of the Year, 2009 (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - 11/30--20 questions, 2009 (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - 12/1--ABC Mike Shaw, 2009 (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - 12/1--Absolut, 2009 (Box 82, Folder 13)
    - 12/1--Levi Dockers, 2009 (Box 82, Folder 14)
    - 12/2--Ameriprise, 2009 (Box 82, Folder 15)
    - 12/2--REO Speedwagon, 2009 (Box 82, Folder 16)
    - 12/3--Puerto Rico, 2009 (Box 82, Folder 17)
    - 12/3--Tiger Woods, 2009 (Box 82, Folder 18)
    - 12/3--Tostitos, 2009 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - 12/7--Harvard School of Public Health, 2009 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - 12/7--Virginia O'Hanlan, 2009 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - 12/7--Zappos, 2009 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - 12/9--GLSEN (Gay, Lesbian andStraight Education Network), 2009 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - 12/9--UBS/Ad spending, 2009 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - 12/10--Advertising publications, 2009 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - 12/13--Tiger Woods, 2009 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Super Bowl, 2009; 2 folders (Box 83, Folder 9-10)
    - Super Bowl--Advertising, 2009 (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Super Bowl--Audi, 2009 (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - Super Bowl--Bridgestone, 2009 (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - Super Bowl--CareerBuilder, 2009 (Box 83, Folder 14)
    - Super Bowl--Cars.com, 2009 (Box 83, Folder 15)
    - Super Bowl--Cash4Gold, 2009 (Box 83, Folder 16)
    - Super Bowl--Castrol, 2009 (Box 83, Folder 17)
    - Super Bowl--"Coattails", 2009 (Box 83, Folder 18)
    - Super Bowl--Coca-Cola, 2009 (Box 83, Folder 19)
    - Super Bowl--Denny's, 2009 (Box 83, Folder 20)
    - Super Bowl--Disney, 2009 (Box 83, Folder 21)
    - Super Bowl--Dreamworks, 2009 (Box 83, Folder 22)
    - Super Bowl--E*Trade, 2009 (Box 83, Folder 23)
    - Super Bowl--Experts, 2009 (Box 83, Folder 24)
    - Super Bowl--Frito-Lay Cheetos/Doritos, 2009 (Box 83, Folder 25)
    - Super Bowl--General Electric, 2009 (Box 83, Folder 26)
    - Super Bowl--GoDaddy.com, 2009 (Box 83, Folder 27)
    - Super Bowl--H, 2009 (Box 83, Folder 28)
    - Super Bowl--Heineken/Anheuser-Busch, 2009 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Super Bowl--Hulu, 2009 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Super Bowl--Hyundai, 2009 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Super Bowl--Kellogg's, 2009 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Super Bowl--Mars/Pedigree, 2009 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Super Bowl--Monster, 2009 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Super Bowl--Movie ads, 2009 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Super Bowl--NBC, 2009 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Super Bowl--NBC/Universal Orlando, 2009 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Super Bowl--New York Times blog, 2009 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Super Bowl--NFL, 2009 (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Super Bowl--Pepsi/Sobe Lifewater, 2009 (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - Super Bowl--Post game polls, 2009 (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - Super Bowl--Previews, 2009 (Box 84, Folder 14)
    - Super Bowl--Teleflora, 2009 (Box 84, Folder 15)
    - Super Bowl--Toyota Venza, 2009 (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - 2010, 5
    - 1/4--Huge/MTV/Hired (series), 2010 (Box 84, Folder 17)
    - 1/6--Chrysler, 2010 (Box 84, Folder 18)
    - 1/8--Sam's Club/Rue 33 vodka, 2010 (Box 84, Folder 19)
    - 1/8--Tide detergent, 2010 (Box 84, Folder 20)
    - 1/11--AFLAC, 2010 (Box 84, Folder 21)
    - 1/11--Opra magazine, 2010 (Box 84, Folder 22)
    - 1/12--American Idol (series), 2010 (Box 84, Folder 23)
    - 1/12--Crowdsourcing, 2010 (Box 84, Folder 24)
    - 1/13--Olympics/Vitamin Water, 2010 (Box 84, Folder 25)
    - 1/13--Super Bowl, 2010 (Box 84, Folder 26)
    - 1/14--Census, 2010 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - 1/15--Haiti, 2010 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - 1/16--Johnny Rockets, 2010 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - 1/17--Progressive Insurance, 2010 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - 1/18--Popular Mechanics, 2010 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - 1/19--Haiti, 2010 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - 1/19--Kirshenbaum Bond Senecal, 2010 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - 1/20--Super Bowl/Focus on the Family, 2010 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - 1/21--Nick Brien/McCann, 2010 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - 1/21--Super Bowl, 2010 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - 1/22--Realism in advertising, 2010 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - 1/25--Monster.com, 2010 (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - 1/25--Univision Upfront, 2010 (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - 1/26--Focus on the Family, 2010 (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - 1/26--Super Bowl/Anheuser-Busch, 2010 (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - 1/26--Super Bowl/Hyundai, 2010 (Box 85, Folder 16)
    - 1/27--Super Bowl/Coca-Cola, 2010 (Box 85, Folder 17)
    - 1/27--Super Bowl/Papa John's, 2010 (Box 85, Folder 18)
    - 1/28--Universal Orlando, 2010 (Box 85, Folder 19)
    - 1/29--Budweiser clydesdales, 2010 (Box 85, Folder 20)
    - 1/29--Disabilities, 2010 (Box 85, Folder 21)
    - 1/29--Valentine's Day, 2010 (Box 85, Folder 22)
    - 2/1--Pepsi, 2010 (Box 85, Folder 23)
    - 2/2--Focus on the Family, 2010 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - 2/3--Method detergent, 2010 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - 2/3--Pizza Hut, 2010 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - 2/3--Super Bowl ad sentiment, 2010 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - 2/5--Super Bowl preview, 2010 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - 2/7--Super Bowl live blog, 2010 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - 2/8--Super Bowl blog, 2010 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - 2/9--Jonathan Bond, 2010 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - 2/9--Super Bowl, 2010 (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - 2/11--ANA Conference, 2010 (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - 2/11--Nationwide, 2010 (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - 2/11--Olympics, 2010 (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - 2/11--Sprite, 2010 (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - 2/11--Super Bowl ad rankings, 2010 (Box 86, Folder 14)
    - 2/16--Snickers, 2010 (Box 86, Folder 15)
    - 2/16--Winter Olympics, 2010 (Box 86, Folder 16)
    - 2/17--Geri Wang/ABC, 2010 (Box 86, Folder 17)
    - 2/17--Rums of Puerto Rico, 2010 (Box 86, Folder 18)
    - 2/18--Gold Bond, 2010 (Box 86, Folder 19)
    - 2/18--Super Bowl postgame, 2010 (Box 86, Folder 20)
    - 2/18--Toyota, 2010 (Box 86, Folder 21)
    - 2/19--Ally Bank, 2010 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - 2/19--Tiger Woods, 2010 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - 2/22--Phelps Group, 2010; 2 folders (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - 2/22--Saks, 2010 (Box 87, Folder 4-5)
    - 2/22--Westin Hotels, 2010 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - 2/25--MTA/Titan, 2010 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - 2/25--Svedka vodka, 2010 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - 2/26--AAAA Conference, 2010 (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - 2/27--Google Brazil, 2010 (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - 3/1--Lowe's, 2010 (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - 3/3--Jon Hamm/Mercedes, 2010 (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - 3/5--Denny's, 2010 (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - 3/5--Oscar survey, 2010 (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - 3/5--Tru TV Upfront, 2010 (Box 87, Folder 15)
    - 3/5--Zappo's, 2010 (Box 87, Folder 16)
    - 3/6--Andrew Jaffee, 2010 (Box 87, Folder 17)
    - 3/8--Good Housekeeping magazine, 2010 (Box 87, Folder 18)
    - 3/9--Linday Lohan/E*Trade, 2010 (Box 87, Folder 19)
    - 3/10--Mad Men/Barbie, 2010 (Box 87, Folder 20)
    - 3/11--Bravo/Nickelodeon Upfront, 2010 (Box 88, Folder 1)